



# Dániel Kukucska

**Date of birth:** 23 Sep 1997 | **Nationality:** Hungarian | **Gender:** Male |

daniel.kukucska.txt@gmail.com https://github.com/danielkukucska

About me:

Experienced Mathematics Teacher with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Public Speaking, Microsoft Office, and Mathematics. In the past years started to work with SharePoint Online, Power Platform and React with TypeScript. Looking forward to dive deeper into frontend development.

### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2009 - 2017

**GRADUTAION CERTIFICATE - Török Ignác High School** 

2017 - 2022

**BUSINESS INFORMATICS BSC -** Corvinus University of Budapest

2022 - CURRENT

**SOFTWARE ENGINEER -** Eszterházy Károly Catholic University

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **HUNGARIAN** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	B2	C1	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2017

**TEACHER - LOGISCHOOL KFT.** 

Teaching the basics of programming for primary school students. We used Scratch in the weekly lectures and in summer camps.

2018 - 2019

**BUSINESS ANALYST - SBERBANK ZRT.** 

Working as an intern in the business application development department. My assigned applications were related to finance and legal departments.

2020 - CURRENT

IT CONSULTANT - COLLABIT ZRT.

At first, my main focus was SharePoint Online, Project Online and Power Platform. Since 2021, I am also working as a frontend developer.

## VOLUNTEERING

2017 - 2022

### **Teacher**

Teaching pre-graduate students for mathematcis in a non-profit student organization. Head of mathematics in the year of 2019/2020.

### DIGITAL SKILLS

# **My Digital Skills**

Frontend development

TypeScript | HTML | JavaScript | React JS. | CSS

Other development related

SQL | Git | NODE is | Basic Knowledge of Azure DevOps

M365

Power platform (Power Apps, Power Automate) | Microsoft Project Online | SharePoint Online